When do you think ‘middle age’ starts?
你认为“中年”始于何时？
What about ‘old age’?
“老年”呢？
Unsurprisingly, the answer to these questions will depend on your culture, as well as how old you are when someone asks you.
不出所料，这些问题的答案会因文化背景而异，同时也取决于被问到这个问题时你的年龄。
What is perhaps more surprising is that the answer to these questions could have an impact on how quickly your body begins to age.
但或许更令人惊讶的是，对这些问题的回答，竟然会影响你身体衰老的速度。
In 2003, the researchers Hannah Kuper and Sir Michael Marmot carried out a wide-ranging study in which participants were asked the question: when does old age start?
2003年，研究人员汉娜·库珀和迈克尔·马尔莫爵士开展了一项大范围研究。研究中，他们向参与者提出了一个问题：老年从什么时候开始？
They then followed up with the participants six to nine years later and found that those who had thought old age began earlier were more likely to be in poor physical health.
六到九年后，研究人员对这些参与者进行了追踪调查，结果发现，那些认为老年到来时间更早的人，身体健康状况不佳的可能性更高。
But how could someone’s answer to a question about age possibly have an impact on their health?
但一个人对年龄相关问题的回答，怎么会影响到自身健康呢？
It might be that the question prompts people to think about their physical health, underlying health issues or poor lifestyle, which might then make them feel that old age is coming sooner.
可能是这个问题促使人们开始审视自己的身体健康状况、潜在的健康隐患或是不良的生活习惯，进而让他们觉得老年正在加速到来。
People who say that old age sets in earlier, may also be more fatalistic and less likely to visit a doctor or to adopt healthier routines.
那些认为老年来得更早的人，或许也更具宿命论思想，他们不太愿意去看医生，也不太会养成更健康的生活习惯。
It’s even possible that the stress of having negative thoughts about ageing, contributes to more health problems.
甚至有可能，对衰老抱有负面想法所产生的压力，会引发更多的健康问题。
So, this is what happens when we think negatively about ageing, but what happens when we think positively?
以上是我们对衰老持消极态度时会出现的情况，那如果我们抱有积极心态，又会怎样呢？
People who think old age starts later, may be more conscious about their health and fitness and therefore take steps to stay in better shape.
那些认为老年开始得更晚的人，可能会更关注自身的健康和体能状况，从而采取措施保持良好的身体状态。
They may see their twilight years as an opportunity to learn new things and make new plans.
他们会把晚年时光看作是学习新事物、制定新计划的机会。
If they believe they are younger, they therefore behave in younger ways, creating a virtuous circle.
如果他们相信自己还很年轻，就会以更年轻化的方式行事，进而形成一个良性循环。
Whatever the reason, according to data from the Ohio Longitudinal Study of Ageing and Retirement, people who think positively about ageing live longer on average.
无论原因是什么，俄亥俄州老龄化与退休纵向研究的数据显示，对衰老持积极态度的人，平均寿命会更长。
Of course, none of this research means that a positive attitude can magically stop the ageing process – our bodies get older with each passing year, after all.
当然，这些研究并不意味着积极的心态能神奇地阻止衰老进程——毕竟，我们的身体每年都在变老。
But it seems that if we try to be healthier and if we believe that there are still things we can do in old age, we might live longer and enjoy ourselves more too.
但似乎可以确定的是，如果我们努力保持健康，并且相信自己在晚年仍然有很多事情可以做，我们就有可能活得更长久，也能更享受生活。